Contact

eskoppe@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-koppe-29785616b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Nursing Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Critical Thinking

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

NIHSS

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Elizabeth Koppe

BSN, RN, CCRN

Tulsa, Oklahoma Area

Summary

Experienced Critical Care, Step-Down, and Med/Surg/Cardiac RN. Specialty certified as a Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN). Bachelors degree in Nursing. Focused on providing research based, quality patient care. Experienced in nursing leadership, having worked as a charge nurse and interim manager. Experienced with Epic, Cerner & Meditech. Highly skilled with specialty critical care equipment such as Ventilators, EVD, CRRT/SLED and Rotoprone beds.

Experience

OSU MEDICAL CENTER
Intensive Care Nurse
June 2020 - Present (1 month)

LiquidAgents Healthcare
Travel Nurse
October 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Saint Francis Health System Charge Nurse June 2019 - March 2020 (10 months)

St. John Health System
ICU RN
July 2016 - October 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Education

University of Oklahoma Health Sciences Center
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016)

Tulsa Community College

Associate of Science - AS, Pre-Nursing Studies